thegwpf.org 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy for www.thegwpf.org | The Global Warming Policy Foundation (GWPF)

We take the privacy of all visitors to this website very seriously and therefore set out in this privacy policy our position regarding certain privacy matters.

Our Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you share with us, or that we collect from you either directly via this Website or via email.

**Information We Collect**

In operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblog statistics and other communication data.

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you register to receive information, our newsletter or to become a member of the GWPF.

Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

**Use of Your Information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is exclusively used to enable us to provide information to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or changes, that may affect our service.

Please note that we do not share any information about identifiable individuals with anyone outside the GWPF.

**Storing Your Personal Data**

We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this Privacy Policy.

Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically. Transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk.

**Third Party Links**

You mind find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

**Contacting Us**

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at [info@thegwpf.org](mailto:info@thegwpf.org). If you prefer to write to us then our contact address is:

The Global Warming Policy Foundation,  
10 Upper Bank Street  
London E14 5NP  
United Kingdom
